1stwishes.com 2008-06-09

# Celebrate Express Privacy Policy

This statement discloses the privacy practices for the Celebrate Express Web site. Questions regarding this statement should be directed to the Celebrate Express Customer Service department by sending an e-mail to [ customerservice@celebrateexpress.com](mailto:customerservice@celebrateexpress.com). 

Celebrate Express is very concerned about the protection of online privacy for all our Web site visitors. Although we track the total number of visitors to our site in an aggregate form to allow us to update and improve our site, personally identifiable information is not extracted in this process. Additionally, customers may use our "Tell A Friend" feature to forward an e-mail to their friends telling them about Celebrate Express, however, we do not retain e-mail addresses captured in this process. 

Our Web site uses Microsoft Site Server technology which allows IP Addresses to be collected and used for administrative purposes, and to analyze traffic patterns for this site. However, no single individual is identified in the analysis of Web traffic. This technology also includes the use of cookies which benefit visitors by saving their information so they don't have to re-type it on subsequent visits to our site. Cookies may be disabled by the user, however, the user would not be able to order products from our site because our shopping cart functionality requires the use of cookies to operate. Orders can always be phoned in by calling 1-800-424-7843. 

We also use pixel tags - tiny graphic images - to tell us what parts of our Web site you have visited and/or to measure the effectiveness of any searches you may do on our site. In addition, we may contract with other companies that use cookies or other online tools such as pixel tags to measure the performance of a marketing effort on our behalf. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and action tags is completely anonymous. 

We make it our top priority to safeguard the privacy of our online customers, and we take great care in making sure that your personal identifiable information is secure. We limit access to personally identifiable information to a very small number of employees who are committed to our privacy and security policies, and who need access to the information in order to perform their jobs. All employees are required to sign a nondisclosure agreement. Any employee who violates our privacy and/or security policies is subject to immediate disciplinary action. 

Celebrate Express collects only personally identifiable data, such as names, addresses, e-mail addresses, and the like, when voluntarily submitted by visitors. We do ask parents/guardians to provide children's birth month and year information so that we may send a Birthday Express catalog at the appropriate time for party planning. 

We also collect payment information in order to bill shoppers for items they ordered. To complete business transactions, credit card numbers are verified by a qualified financial institution using secure encryption technology before an order is shipped. 

In some instances, when an e-mail address has been provided by the visitor (age 18 or older), we will send notices to the visitor, usually in the form of e-mail. These periodic notices will announce the status of an order or Web site changes. Information submitted by visitors who sign up for our Birthday Club is collected in a separate area of our site than information submitted by customers who are placing product orders. While we may communicate with visitors via e-mail about their order, we will not send promotional e-mails unless the visitor has specifically chosen to receive such messages. We do not share e-mail addresses with third parties. 

If you supply us with your postal address online you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please [click here](http://www.celebrateexpress.com/celebration/Pages/CustomerService/Unsubscribe.aspx), and we will remove you from our mailing list. If you have placed an order with our company, we may share your information with other reputable companies so that you may receive mailings and other offers from those companies for products or services we think you might find interesting. However, if you would like to have your name put on our do-not-share list, please [click here](http://www.celebrateexpress.com/celebration/Pages/CustomerService/Unsubscribe.aspx) and we will be sure your name is removed from the list we share with other carefully selected organizations. 

If you do not wish to receive marketing-related e-mail from us, you may opt-out by [clicking here](http://www.celebrateexpress.com/celebration/Pages/CustomerService/Unsubscribe.aspx) and we will quickly honor your request. You may also opt-out by postal mail by sending your request to Celebrate Express, 11232 120th Ave NE Ste 204, Kirkland, WA 98033, or by phoning our Customer Service department at 1-800-424-7843. Online contests and sweepstakes may have alternate rules regarding contact information. Please refer to the individual guidelines posted for each promotion. 

If you would like to make changes to the personally identifiable information you previously submitted to us, (e.g. your name or address), you may send an e-mail with the revised information to [ customerservice@celebrateexpress.com](mailto:customerservice@celebrateexpress.com), or call our Customer Service department at 1-800-424-7843. 

Periodically, Celebrate Express will send new issues of our online newsletter to individuals via e-mail. Newsletters contain seasonal, birthday and special occasion party ideas and special promotions. Each newsletter also includes an opt-out feature which allows you to opt-out of receiving the newsletter at any time. Individuals who supply us with their e-mail address and/or physical mailing address via our online product request form may be notified via e-mail or physical mailing address in response to their inquiry. 

Persons who supply us with their telephone number(s) online may receive a telephone contact from us with information regarding orders they have placed online. When providing your telephone number, please provide both the area code and phone number. Your phone number will not be shared with anyone. 

Parents and guardians: We want to help you guard your children's privacy. Celebrate Express does not collect any personal information on those sections of the site that may be considered designed for the use of children under the age of 13. We encourage you to talk to your children about safe and responsible use of their personal information while using the Internet. 

We reserve the right to change this policy at any time by notifying guests of the existence of a new privacy policy. If we change the way we use personally identifiable information, we will notify you via e-mail within 30 days and wait for your consent before taking further action regarding your personally identifiable information.
